(Sheldon:)Well, first, I think the fact
(Sheldon:)that you use your birthday
as a password is embarrassing.
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Second...
(Sheldon:)I thought your paper was inspired.
(Arthur:)Oh, well, that...
that means a lot to me.
(Sheldon:)Can I invite you in for tea?
No, no. I really... I have to run.
(Penny:)Hey, Arthur. How are you?
(Arthur:)Well, I guess one cup wouldn't hurt.
(Howard:)Hey, buddy, what's up?
(Raj:)Well, I was feeling bad
about how I acted the other night
(Raj:)so I made you a little something.
(Howard:)-You didn't have to do that.
-Well, it was fun.
I used some of the jewelry techniques
you taught us.
it's a lightsaber belt buckle.
(Howard:)This is so cool. Thanks.
It gets better.